https://www.hiphampers.com.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy | Hip Hampers
1800 008 100
0
Your shopping cart is empty.
0
Added to cart.
Privacy policy
1. By using our Website or registering for an account with us, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy, and you are consenting to our collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.
2. We appreciate that your privacy is important to you and we will continue to protect the personal information you provide us and we will manage your personal information in compliance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs).
3. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment.
When do we collect information?
4. We do not automatically collect personal information from you, such as your name, address, phone number, email address or other personally identifiable information about you (personal information). We collect three categories of information when you use our website:
(a) the personal information you voluntarily provide — that is, we collect personal information with your informed consent;(b) anonymous non-personal information about how you use our website; and
(c) “cookie” based information that makes your use of our website easier by recording your preferences so that when you return to our website the “cookie” re-loads that information into your web browser.
5. For example, we will collect personal information from you when you register on our websites, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a promotional offer, competition or survey or fill out a form related to any customer service feature operating on our websites.
6. When you become a subscriber to the Hip Hampers® Newsletter you will need to provide certain details so that we can establish and manage your customer account.
7. When you log-into our website using your Google or Facebook log-in (or use any other log-in connected to any other social media platform) you are allowing that social media platform to share your personal information with us (that is, your personal information related to your log-in with that social media platform, which may include your email address and other personal information).
Why do we need to collect personal information?
8. We collect personal information when you volunteer that information in order to receive a service from our website. The personal information collected on our websites will be used to provide the services you have requested, such as setting up and managing your subscription to the Hip Hampers® Newsletter, or processing any purchases you may make on the Website. Your personal information may be used in relation to any survey, promotional offer or any competition you may enter on our websites.
What information do we collect?
9. The type of information we collect from you will depend on what services on our website that you use. The personal information we may collect includes your name, postal address, email address, telephone numbers and contact details and information for identification purposes. If you make online purchases from the Hip Hampers® website by credit card or debit card or direct debit from your bank account we will collect your card or bank account details.
10. General information about visits to our websites is collected by our computer servers, with small files (cookies) that our websites transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow the delivery of cookies). The cookies are used to follow the pattern of movements of users by letting us know which pages on our websites are visited, in what order and how often and the previous website visited and also to process the items you select if you are making purchases from the Hip Hampers® website. The anonymous non-personal information that when collect and analyse in not personal information as described in the Privacy Act.
Why do we use cookies and other web use tracking technologies?
11. When you access our website, a small files containing a unique identification (ID) number may be downloaded by your web browser and stored in the cache of your computer. The purpose of sending these files with a unique ID number is so that our website can recognise your computer when you next visit our website. The cookies that are shared with your computer can’t be used to discover any personal information such as your name, address or email address they merely identify your computer to our websites when you visit us.
12. We can also log the internet protocol address (IP address) of visitors to our website so that we can work out the countries in which the computers are located.
13. We collect information using cookies and other tracking technologies for the following reasons:
(a) to help us monitor the performance of our website so that we can improve the operation of the website and the services we offer;(b) to provide personalised services to each user of our website to make their navigation through our website easier and more rewarding to the user;
(c) to sell advertising on the website in order to meet some of the costs of operating the website and improve the content on the website; and
(d) when we have permission from the user, to market the services we provide by sending emails that are personalised to what we understand are the interests of the user.
14. Even if you have given us permission to send you emails, you can, at any time, decide not to receive further emails and will be able to unsubscribe from that service.
15. If you are unhappy about having a cookie sent to you, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent. However, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly, however, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting us on our telephone number.
How do we store your information?
16. We use different technologies and procedures to help protect personal information from unauthorized access, loss, alternation, disclosure or use. Some of the safeguards we use are physical access controls, information firewalls and access authorisation controls to where your personal information is held in data centres. We also use data encryption when personal information is transferred to and from our service providers. Our commitment to data security means:
(a) we have procedures to limit access to personal information within our organisation;(b) we use security measures and technologies within our organisation to protect your personal information; and
(c) we use service providers that can establish that they have secure controls relating to software security, access security and network security, including where credit card information is being transferred.
17. Whilst our website is hosted in Australia, web traffic information we collect, such as data collected by Google Analytics may be stored overseas.
What use do we make of your personal information?
18. We will communicate with you in relation to any purchases you make from the Hip Hampers® website.
19. We may send you information and updates about any other product, service or information that we provide to our customers. In addition we may send you occasional company news and information about other products and services or special promotional offers of our affiliated companies. If at any time you would like to stop receiving future commercial messages from us, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
20. We may also release your personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, website policies and/or these Terms & Conditions, or to protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.
How can I access the personal information that you collect?
21. We are happy to provide you with details of personal information held about you. APP 12 allows you to get access to, and correct, the personal information we hold about you.
22. To access this information, you need to email or write to us using the contact details below. Please also include your name and order details (if available).
23. APP 13 allows you to ask us to take reasonable steps to correction any personal information that is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading.
24. If you believe that your personal information has been misused, you can inform us of your complaint by writing to our address and we will attempt to resolve the matter.
Please contact us on the details below:
Mail:
ATTN: Privacy Policy
Hip Hampers® Pty Ltd
PO Box 302
WILLOUGHBY NSW 2068
Telephone: 1800 008 100
Email: sales@hiphampers.com.au
25. If you are not satisfied with the outcome of your complaint you may refer the matter to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (OAIC). Visit the OAIC complaints page at http://www.oaic.gov.au/privacy/privacy-complaints or telephone: 1300 363 992 or email enquiries@oaic.gov.au.
Third party links
26. Our websites may include links to websites operated by third parties. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our websites and welcome any comment about linked websites.
Terms and Conditions
27. Please also read our Terms and Conditions which sets out the conditions of use and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website.
Your Consent
28. By using our Website, you consent to this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
29. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
30. This Privacy Policy was last modified on 5 February 2018.
HampersCorporate Hampers
The Full Collection
Luxury Range
Christmas Hampers
AboutMeet the team
Gifting tips
Testimonials
InformationDelivery information
Bulk order
Terms and conditions
Privacy policy
Your accountYour cart
We accept
Follow us
Please wait...
Hip Hampers® is a trademark of Hip Hampers Pty Ltd; registered in Australia.
© Hip Hampers 2018. All rights reserved.
×
Branded Corporate Wrap
You have no or insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option or contact us on 1 800 008 100 to organise your corporate design.
×
Branded Corporate WrapYou have insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded Corporate WrapHip Hampers fully design your cello glazed branded hamper wraps.
Once these are designed Hip Hampers will hold these in stock for your company.
The wraps can then be used across our full range of Corporate Hampers to fully promote your brand when gifting.
If Hip Hampers have already designed your wrap and you have not logged in, please login to your account to be able to place an order.
To find out more information and to order Branded Hamper Wraps visit our Corporate Gifting Page.
Contact us on 1800 008 100.
×
Branded CandleHip Hampers fully design your branded candles.
Once these are designed Hip Hampers will hold these in stock for your company.
The candles can then be used within any candle hamper within our Corporate Hamper range to fully promote your brand when gifting.
If Hip Hampers have already designed your candle and you have not logged in, please login to your account to be able to place an order.
To find out more information and to order Branded Candles visit our Corporate Gifting Page.
Contact us on 1800 008 100.
×
Branded CandleYou have no or insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded CandleYou have insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded Big Chop CheeseboardHip Hampers fully design your Branded Big Chop Cheeseboards.
Once these are designed Hip Hampers will hold these in stock for your company.
The Branded Big Chop Cheeseboards can then be used to replace any unbranded Big Chop Cheeseboards within our Corporate Hamper range to fully promote your brand when gifting.
If Hip Hampers have already designed your Branded Big Chop Cheeseboards and you have not logged in, please login to your account to be able to place an order.
To find out more information and to order Branded Big Chop Cheeseboards visit our Corporate Gifting Page.
Contact us on 1800 008 100.
×
Branded Big Chop CheeseboardYou have no or insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded Big Chop CheeseboardYou have insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded Provincial CheeseboardHip Hampers fully design your Branded Provincial Cheeseboards.
Once these are designed Hip Hampers will hold these in stock for your company.
The Branded Provincial Cheeseboards can then be used to replace any unbranded Provincial Cheeseboards within our Luxury and Corporate Hamper ranges to fully promote your brand when gifting.
If Hip Hampers have already designed your Branded Provincial Cheeseboard and you have not logged in, please login to your account to be able to place an order.
To find out more information and to order Branded Provincial Cheeseboards visit our Corporate Gifting Page.
Contact us on 1800 008 100.
×
Branded Provincial CheeseboardYou have no or insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Branded Provincial CheeseboardYou have insufficient stock available in your account. Place an order now or if you have recently placed an order, please wait to receive notification that the stock is available in your account. Alternatively you may continue with this order by selecting the unbranded option.
×
Get Branded Corporate WrapCall Hip Hampers to get Branded Corporate Wrap
You must login to use the previous details.
